Guide to the Artists Space Archive MSS.291
Fales Library and Special Collections
Artists Space Archive
1973-2009
Fales Library and Special Collections
Sandler, Irving, 1925-2018
Artists Space (Gallery)
MSS.291
40.25 Linear Feet
The original goal of Artists Space was to support young, emerging artists, specifically those who had not yet had a solo show in New York City. Artists Space became one of the most influential alternative non-profit arts spaces in the Downtown New York scene, hosting a variety of prominent exhibitions including Adrian Piper's "It's Just Art" (1981), Nan Goldin's "Witnesses: Against Our Vanishing" (1989), Douglas Crimp's "Pictures" (1977), and Michael Asher's "Untitled" (1988). The bulk of the material is exhibition files, and includes research files, coordination, opening, reception, sales, touring, and dismantling. This collection also preserves artists' materials (CVs, catalogues, photographic elements), correspondence, drafts of published works, financial records, gallery floorplans and maps, grant applications, loan and legal documentation, and promotional matter in the form of brochures, postcard announcements, newsletters, posters, and press releases.
Scope and Content
Materials in the Artists Space Archive document the workings of this late-twentieth-century art organization and all its attendant functions. Because exhibitions are at the core of Artists Space programming, the bulk of this material includes files that record exhibition research, coordination, opening, reception, sales, touring, and dismantling. This collection also preserves artists' materials (CVs, catalogues, photographic elements), correspondence, drafts of published works, financial records, gallery floorplans and maps, grant applications, loan and legal documentation, and promotional matter in the form of brochures, postcard announcements, newsletters, posters, and press releases. Documentation of Artists Space events and exhibition programming are also preserved in the form of images: slides and prints, drawings, paintings and collages, floppy disks, zip disks, cd-roms, and other digital media containing images, films, and audio. The research materials for the Artists Space 15th and 25th Anniversary publications also provide an instructive history of the organization.
Provenance
The Artists Space Archive was donated to NYU's Fales Library and Special Collections in two batches, in 2010 and 2011.
Historical Note
Artists Space (originally called the Committee on Visual Arts, Inc.) was founded in 1972 by arts administrator Trudie Grace and critic Irving Sandler as a pilot project for the New York State Council on the Arts (NYSCA). The original goal of the Committee was to support young, emerging artists, specifically those who had not yet had a solo show in New York City. Quickly thereafter, Artists Space became financially independent of the State Council and over the years became one of the most influential alternative non-profit arts spaces in the Downtown New York Scene. Artists Space's original guidelines stipulated that well-known artists would select other artists to exhibit. Throughout the years, the gallery discarded this model, but retained the "Artists Select Artists" model for one show a year. Throughout the years, Artists Space, as a non-profit arts organization, has retained its commitment to exhibiting new and experimental artworks, and has expanded its scope to include readings, panel discussions, film programs, and special series, including the International Projects Program, Selections from the Artists File, and others. Artists Space moved from its original location at 155 Wooster Street to 105 Hudson Street in 1977, to 223 West Broadway in 1984, and to its current location at 38 Greene Street in 1993.
Provocative programming has been the hallmark of Artists Space throughout its history, and a variety of prominent exhibitions are well-represented in the collection, including Adrian Piper's "It's Just Art" (1981), Nan Goldin's "Witnesses: Against Our Vanishing" (1989), Douglas Crimp's "Pictures" (1977), and Michael Asher's "Untitled" (1988). "Witnesses: Against Our Vanishing" sparked controversy, when, due to an objection to an essay by David Wojnarowicz in the catalogue, the National Endowment for the Arts pulled its funding in the wake of Newt Gingrich's moral crusade in Congress. The attendant controversy is well-documented in the collection. Artists Space has also given many artists their first chance at the spotlight, amongst them: Joan Jonas, Cindy Sherman, Jeff Koons, Sherrie Levine, Louise Lawler, Laurie Anderson, Barbara Bloom, John Miller, John Baldessari, Jack Smith, Andrea Fraser, Haim Steinbach, Tim Rollins, Lyle Ashton Harris, Ashley Bickerton, Peter Halley, Lari Pittman, Group Material, Stuart Sherman, Barbara Kruger, Laurie Simmons, Anthony McCall, Fred Wilson, Felix Gonzalez-Torres, Mike Kelly, Judith Barry, Michael Smith, Robert Longo, and Jenny Holzer.
For a full list of the exhibition history of the gallery, please see: http://artistsspace.org/archive
Arrangement
All efforts were made to preserve the original arrangement of the collection. The collection has been divided into eight series reflecting this arrangement. Within each series, items are arranged chronologically by event or exhibition opening date. The Book Files series is an exception, and is arranged alphabetically, then chronologically. The Media series is also an exception in which items are arranged alphabetically. The archivist transcribed folder titles exactly from original folder titles given by the organization. When they were changed, due to error or omission, they are denoted with brackets. The researcher should expect to find overlapping of materials throughout all series. Oversized archival materials from the various series are listed at the end of the finding aid. The first seven series are available for research while access copies of the media originals are not available. This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I: Exhibition Files
Series II: Promotional Materials
Series III: Administrative Files
Subseries A: Gallery Organization
Subseries B: Workshops
Series IV: Book Files
Series V: Independent Project Grants
Series VI: Curator Files
Series VII: Photographic Materials
Series VIII: Media
Subseries A: Sound recordings, video recordings, and films
Subseries B: Data Storage
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open with some restrictions. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
A.I.R. Gallery Archive (MSS.184)
Andrea Callard Papers (MSS.156)
Annina Nosei Gallery Papers (MSS.298)
Christopher D'Arcangelo Papers (MSS.264)
Creative Time Archive (MSS.179)
David Wojnarowicz Papers (MSS.092)
Downtown Flyers and Invitations Collection (MSS.119)
Exit Art Archive (MSS.343)
Fashion Moda Archive (MSS.091)
Frank Moore Papers (MSS.135)
Group Material Archive (MSS.215)
Jaime Davidovich Collection (MSS.155)
Lynne Tillman Papers (MSS.180)
The Mix Collection (MSS.143)
Public Art Fund Archive (MSS.270)
REPOhistory Archive (MSS.113)
Richard Foreman Papers (MSS.152)
Robert Blanchon Papers and Collection (MSS.220)
Ron Kolm Papers (MSS.079)
Sylvere Lotringer Papers and Semiotext(e) Archive (MSS.221)
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Audiovisual and born-digital materials have not been preserved and may not be accessible to researchers.
CD-Rs.; Artists' writings; Invitations.; Negatives (photographic); Exhibition catalogs.; Correspondence.; VHS; DVDs.; Art and society -- United States -- History -- 20th century.; Résumés (personnel records); Art galleries (institutions); Performance art -- New York (State) -- New York.; Art -- Exhibitions.; Alternative spaces (Arts facilities) -- New York (State) -- New York.; Artists -- New York (State) -- New York.; Video art -- United States.; Photographs.; Artists and community -- United States; Slides (photographs); Administrative records.; Promotional materials; Press kits.; Press releases.; Smith, Jack, 1932-1989; Steinbach, Haim, 1944-; Miller, John; Baldessari, John, 1931-2020; Harris, Lyle Ashton; Lawler, Louise; Kruger, Barbara, 1945-; Koons, Jeff, 1955-; Levine, Sherrie; Sherman, Stuart, 1945-2001; Bickerton, Ashley, 1959-; Gonzalez-Torres, Félix, 1957-1996; Barry, Judith; Goldin, Nan, 1953-; Bloom, Barbara; Crimp, Douglas; Asher, Michael; Jonas, Joan; Fraser, Andrea; Rollins, Tim, 1955-; Group Material (Firm: New York, N.Y.); Simmons, Laurie; Piper, Adrian, 1948-; Holzer, Jenny, 1950-; Sherman, Cindy; Anderson, Laurie, 1947-; Wilson, Fred, 1954-; McCall, Anthony; Pittman, Lari, 1952-; Halley, Peter; Sandler, Irving, 1925-2018; Longo, Robert; Smith, Michael, 1951-; Kelly, Mike
- Series I: Exhibition Files, 1973 - 2009
  Scope and Content
  This series consists of materials generated by the production of exhibitions and events at Artists Space from 1973-2009. Comprising the bulk of the collection, this material includes notes, correspondence, budgets, artists' CVs and slides, press releases, loan forms, exhibition inventories, architectural plans, travel itineraries, press packets, announcement cards, brochures, press clippings, and research materials related to the exhibitions at Artists Space. There is also extensive documentation of many of the exhibitions and events, through correspondence and exhibition images. Particular strengths include material related to the controversial Witnesses: Against our Vanishing exhibition, the national tour of Putt Modernism, the Artists Select series, the AIDS forum, and many more.
  Arrangement
  The original order of this series has been retained, which is chronological by the opening date of the exhibition, where known. For a full list of the exhibition history of the gallery, please see: http://artistsspace.org/archive
  - Seasons 1 - 7 Exhibition and Events Lists, 1973 - 1980 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - JB Cobb, Martha Edelheit, Ree Morton, October 6, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Binion, Borofsky, Obering, November 3, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Barbara Kruger, January 5, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Laurie Anderson, Don Gummer, Barbara Kruger, January 5, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Mel Kendrick, Lois Lane, Chris Shelton, February 2, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Evening Events at A.S., February 1974 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Sidney Geist, Marvin Torfield, John Torreano, March 2, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Group Show, May 9, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Judy Pfaff, Gwynn Murrill, Don Wynn, October 5, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Albert M. Fine, November 2, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Room 207: Press Release, November 5, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - James Biederman, Thomas Lanigan Schmidt, Charles Simonds, December 7, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Meryl Vladimer, Ted Stamm, Louise Chase, January 4, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Judy Rifka, Ernesto Silva, Deb Freeman, February 1, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Joseph Marioni, Andrew Ginzel, Barbara Schwartz, March 1, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Henrietta Bagley, Susan Heinemann, April 5, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Albert Terris: Recent Works in Steel, April 5, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Group Show, Painting and Sculpture, May 3, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - United Graffiti Artist: Exhibition Catalogue, September 9, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Marc Blane, Ken Hubbell, Carole Stein, October 4, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Events: Critics Responsibility to the Artist, November 5, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Ruth Hardinger, Richard Klauber, November 8, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Events: Simone Forti, Peter Van Riper Announcement, November 14, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Scott Burton, Pamela Jenrette, December 6, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Connie Beckley, December 12, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Philip Smith, December 16, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Events: Cynthia Carlson Announcement, December 18, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Artists Film Series: Vito Acconci, Dan Graham, Jack Golstein, January 1976 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Sigrid Burton, Bruce Colvin, Ellen Phelan, January 10, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Lauren Euring, Susan Leites, Inverna Lockpaz, February 7, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Events: Theodora Skipitares Announcement, February 22, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Artists Film Series: Lawrence Weiner Announcement, February 27, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Susan Eder, Matt Mullican, March 6, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Artists Film Series: David Lamelas Announcement, March 12, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Events: Valery Taylor Map Reading Announcement, March 13, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Artists Film Series: Robert Morgan, Chris Langdon Announcements, March 19, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Gerry Morehead, Jim Pavlicovic, April 3, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Panel Discussion Art and Class, April 9, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Events: Martha Wilson "Rose" Performance Announcement, April 23, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Events: Marcel Just "Showing the Outline" Performance Announcement, April 24, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Artists Film Series: Diego Cortez, David Shulman Announcements, April 2, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Gary Bower, Fontaine Dunn, Hermine Ford, May 1, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Events: Gradual Progress, A Collaboration - Wendy Greenberg, Elaine Hartnett, Maureen Conner Announcements, May 9, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Events: Failure, Ideology, and the World Order, a talk by Alan Sondheim Announcements, May 14, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Artists Film Series: Robert Attanasio Program, May 28, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Eleanor Magid, Tony Vevers, William White, June 5, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Events: "Trespass" Situations by Scott Billingsley Announcements, June 11, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Barbara Bloom, David Salle, September 18, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - TR Performance Series, October 15, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Performance Series: Poppy Johnson, October 15, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Performance Series: Donn Aron: A Strategy for Two Players, October 16, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Performance Series: "Things I Will regret", "Temptation to Exit" by Robert Longo Announcements, October [17], 1976 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Performance Series: "Busmans Holiday Retreat Revue" by Michael Smith, October 26, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Performance Series: "Wait" by Robin Winters, October 22, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Performance Series: Amy Taubin "Superimpositions" (never-to-be shot footage), October 23, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Performance Series: Susan Russell "Magnolia", October 24, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Performance Series: Michael McClard "Clamor Clobber Comb", October 27, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Performance Series: Martha Wilson "Mudpie", October 29, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Performance Series: Marcel Just "Gimme a Break", October 30, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Anthony McCall: "Films", November 3, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Hallwalls, Artists Space Exhibitions, November 6, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Artists Film Series: Michael Harvey Announcements, November 10, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Performance Series: Kevin Boyle "Trace", November 13, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Events: Vincent Trasov (aka Mr. Peanut) and John Mitchell, November 19, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Beth Anderson with Paul Cotton [1 of 2], November 20, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Performance Series: Cid Collins "AMASS" (Grace Jag Stacks Grace), November 30, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Group Exhibition and Silent Auction: Catalogues, December 10, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Artists Film Series: Charles Ahearn, Jill Ciment Announcements, December 17, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Performance Series: Tannis Hugill "Dialogues with a Single Performer" Announcements, December 18, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - New Art Auction and Exhibition Catalogue and Announcements, January 7, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - New Art Auction: Photographic Materials [1 of 2], January 7, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - New Art Auction: Photographic Materials [2 of 2], January 7, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - New Art Auction: Completed Loan and Contracts with Artists, January 3, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Sales Records for Auction, January 7, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Artists for Auction Exhibition: Administrative, Pointer's Card, January 7, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - John Mendelson, Dan Sultan, February 2, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Room 207: Jack Smith "Slide Show" Announcements, February 4, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Robert Morgan, March 5, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Room 207: Taka Iimura [1 of 2], March 29, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Michael Brewster: An Acoustic Sculpture, A Clicker Drawing, April 2, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Room 207: Shows Scheduled, Announcements, Applications, Spring 1977 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Events: Charlemagne Palestine "Battling the Invisible" Announcement and Press, April 16, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Events: David Hykes with the Harmonics Choir, April 29, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Artists Super 8 Film Exposition, May 11, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 1)
  - Artists Super 8 Film Exposition: Schedule II, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 2)
  - Artists Super 8 Film Exposition: Schedule III, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 3)
  - Artists Super 8 Film Exposition: Schedule IV, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 4)
  - Artists Super 8 Film Exposition: Photographic Materials, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 5)
  - Artists Super 8 Film Exposition: "Notes on Bob and Nancy" by Marcia Hafy, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 6)
  - Events: Ralston Farina Announcements, May 22, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 7)
  - Pictures: Works in the Exhibition Checklist and Pricelist, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 8)
  - Pictures: Loan Agreements, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 9)
  - Pictures: Catalogue Text, September 24, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 10)
  - Pictures: Press Packet, September 24, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 11)
  - Pictures: Exhibition Catalogues, Photographic Materials, Press, September 24, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 12)
  - Pictures: Packing List, Condition and Installation Book, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 13)
  - Pictures: National Distillers Correspondence, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 14)
  - Pictures: Travel Correspondence and Insurance, September 29, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 15)
  - Pictures: New York, Ohio, Colorado Announcements, Press Releases, 1978 (Box 228, Folder 16)
  - Performance Series, November 5, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 17)
  - Performance Series: Madeleine Burnside "GLYPHS", November 5, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 18)
  - Performance Series: Jill Kroesen "Previews of Lou and Walter", November 12, 1977 (Box 228, Folder 19)
  - Performance Series: Ann Wooster "Meditations on the Alphabet", November 11, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Performance Series: Julia Heyward "This is my Blue Period", November 26, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Silent Auction: Selection and Correspondence, December 10, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Silent Auction: Auction Contact Sheets and Velox for Catalogue, December 10, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Silent Auction and Group Show: Loan Forms and Contracts, December 10, 1977 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Norma Jean Deak "Travel Log": Performance Announcement, January 8, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Audio Works, January 21, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Audio Works: (Travel) Archive, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Audio Works: (Travel) Catalogue Rough Draft, Correspondence re: catalogue, 1978 - 1979 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Artists Films: Correspondence, March 17, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Artist Films: Promotional Materials, March 17, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - ArtpArkArt III: Announcement, March 18, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Architectural Manifestos: Bernard Tschumi Promotional Materials [1 of 2], April 8, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Bernard Tschumi: Arts Review Magazine, April 8, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Bernard Tschumi: Correspondence, April 8, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Room 207: Christina Rupp, April 8, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Guidlines: Krzysztof Wodiczko, April 29, 1978 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Bands: New Wave Rock Tuesdays, May 2, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Traditions: Five Painters - Budget and Press Release, May 13, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Traditions: Five Painters - Catalogues, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Traditions: Five Painters - Correspondence, February 1978 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Traditions: Five Painters - Images, May 13, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Room 207: Bart Robbett - Two Installations "The Queen's Rules Suspended Brachiating" Announcements, May 1978 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Wall Pieces: Alain Middleton, June 10, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Stuart Sherman's Eleventh Spectacle - The Erotic, September 19, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Four Person Exhibition - Louise Lawler, Adrian Piper, Cindy Sherman, Christopher D'Arcangelo, September 23, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Eric Bogosian's "The Garden" [1 of 2], November 2, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Frederica Marangoni: "In Loving Memory of Art", November 7, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Jim Pomeroy: "Mozart's Moog: Nocturne and Apollo Jest", "Making the World Safe for Geometry", and Projection Piece/Defense Mechanisms", November 9, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Donald Lipski, Richard Jarden, Peter D'Agostino, November 11, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Room 207: Peter D'Agostino "Alpha, Trans, Chung", December 2, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Michael Smith: "Down in the Rec Room", December 19, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Mel Andringa: "Babylon/34th Street", December 21, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Laurie Simmons: Photographs, January 6, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Pieter Holstein: "The Waterfall" [1 of 2], January 6, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - RM Fischer: "Served Up!", January 6, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Artists Draw: Tom Martin, Auste Peciura, Alan Saret, Patti Smith, Nancy Spero, January 6, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Artists Draw: Tom Martin, Auste Peciura, Alan Saret, Patti Smith, Nancy Spero, January 6, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Ken Feingold: "Place, (title to be determined), for a Participant", January 27, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Barbara Levy: Photographs, February 17, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Room 207: Dennis Adams "Patricia Hearst - a Second Reading", February 17, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Donald Newman: "The Nigger Drawings", February 16, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Donald Newman: Correspondence (Originals), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Donald Newman: Correspondence (Copies), 1979 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Donald Newman's Letter, April 7, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Donald Newman: "Open Letter to All Artists" by Artists Space, April 28, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - James Casabere: "Life Story Number 1", February 17, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Anthony Thompson, March 17, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Four Scottish Artists: James Birrell, Michael Davey, Gareth Fischer, Thomas Lawson, March 17, 1979 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - John Gordon, April 7, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - April Performance and Film Series, April 21, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Room 207: Michael Zwack "The Levitation of Anna", May 5, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - William Leavitt: Installation and Drawings, May 5, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Ken Wade: Installation/New York, May 26, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - ART from the British Left, June, 16 1979 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - 16 Artists, September 22, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Martin Cohen, September 27, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Film at Artists Space, November 14, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Gary Burnley, Martin Cohen, Candace Hill, Lewis Stein, Haim Steinbach, November 27, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Candace Hill-Montgomery, November 27, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Gary Burnley, November 27, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Haim Steinbach: Display #7, November 27, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Lewis Stein, November 27, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Freya Hansell: Installation, January 5, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Ken Goodman: Paintings, January 5, 1980 (Box 8, Folder 16)